mrconservative.com 2017-02-18

# Privacy Policy | MrConservative.com | Mr. Conservative is the top website for news, political cartoons, breaking news, republican election news, conservative facts and commentary on political elections

**PRIVACY POLICY**

 _Effective and Last Modified: July 30, 2013_ ****

We understand your privacy is important to you.   Accordingly, except as set forth in this policy, Mr. Conservative does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

This policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes what personal information (“Your Information”)  is collected when you visit mrconservative.com and related websites (the “Website(s)”), and how it is used or disclosed by mrconservative.com or its subsidiary entities (collectively, “Mr. Conservative”).   Please note that by visiting our Websites, you consent to the collection and use of Your Information by Mr. Conservative as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 **1.          Disclosure of Personal Information to Outside Parties:**

Mr. Conservative may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related Website information to third-party vendors. Generally, these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  Mr. Conservative may also release Your Information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with the law, (ii) enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules, or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Mr. Conservative, our users, or others.  We may also give some or all of Your Information to third-party vendors who assist us in fulfilling some of the functions of this Website, or as further set forth below.

 **Information We Collect and How We Use It** **:**

a)      **_Voluntary Information You Provide Us_** **.**   If you contact us by email, complete our registration forms, surveys, or entry forms, subscribe to our services or newsletters or participate in any of our contests or sweepstakes, we will ask you for Your Information, or in some cases, your information will be automatically pre-populated on our forms.  Your Information in this context may include contact information (such as your name and email address) and/or demographic information (such as your zip code or age).  Below you will find descriptions of how Mr. Conservative may use these types Your Information.

b) **  _Confirmed Opt-In_.**  Mr. Conservative acquires no personal or registration data about our users except what you explicitly and voluntarily provide (i.e., via opt-in).  We reserve the right to use this information specifically for the purposes related to your registration in addition to any other purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy.

c)      **_Registration Data_** **.   **Registration data is voluntary personal information provided in order to receive optional access to certain services or Website areas and which may include information such as your name, age, email address, zip code or telephone number.  In addition, registration data may include preference information such as usernames, passwords, desired newsletters, etc.  Here are some of the ways we might use Your Information in this context:

  * To deliver services such as newsletters, offers, message boards, forums and other items;
  * To help us create and deliver the content that is most relevant to you;
  * To alert you to news, events, contests, and other items if you so request;
  * To allow you entrance into restricted areas of the Website, as appropriate;
  * To send you information about Mr. Conservative and our Websites;
  * To compile statistics and conduct basic research; and
  * To give to third parties, such as our advertisers and content partners, who may send you promotional material.

d)      **_Optional Information_** **.**   Sometimes Mr. Conservative posts optional surveys or petitions in which we ask for Your Information (“Your Optional Information”).  The choice is yours – you don’t have to answer surveys or participate in petitions, but if you do, please understand that Mr. Conservative may use Your Optional Information and we may share Your Optional Information with third parties.  If we’re asking for Your Optional Information, we may mark it as such so that you can skip that portion if you would like.  Here are some ways we might use Your Optional Information in this context:

  * To deliver services such as newsletters, offers, message boards, forums and other items;
  * To send you information about Mr. Conservative and our Websites;
  * To help us create and deliver the content that is most relevant to you;
  * To compile statistics and conduct basic research; and
  * To give to third parties, such as our advertisers and content partners, who may send you promotional material.

e)      **_Contests, Sweepstakes and Promotions_**.  From time to time Mr. Conservative runs contests and sweepstakes in which we ask for Your Information, which may include but is not limited to your name, age, email address, and telephone number, so we can determine if you’re eligible for the contest and to notify you if you win.  Sometimes we request additional information such as your gender, marital status and income level.  Here are some of the ways we might use Your Information in this context:

  * To determine if you’re eligible for the contest;
  * To notify you if you’re a winner;
  * To help us create and deliver the content that is most relevant to you;
  * To compile statistics and conduct basic research; and
  * To give to third parties, such as our advertisers and content partners, who may send you promotional material.

f)      **_Special Offers_** ** _.   _**From time to time, Mr. Conservative and its affiliated entities are able to provide to you special offers of products and services. When providing these offers, we need to gather Your Information, which may include but is not limited to your name, age, email address and telephone number. Your acceptance of these offers is completely voluntary, but if you do not correctly provide Your Information as required, you may not receive the product or service offered.  Here is how we may use Your Information in this context:

  * To deliver services that you request or purchase such as newsletters, offers, message boards, forums and other items;
  * To ensure proper delivery of the product or service;
  * To view statistics and conduct basic research;
  * To give to third parties, including radio stations and select parties on our Website, who may send you promotional material;

  * To compile statistics and conduct basic research; and
  * .To give to third parties, who may send you information about their products and services.

g)       **_Online Commerce Services._**   This Website may offer shopping and other online commerce services, which may be offered by Mr. Conservative or by a firm that operates a store under contract with us. If our Website offers such services, you will use a customer order form to request information, products, and services. The order form will ask you to give us contact information (e.g., name or email address), financial information (e.g., account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (e.g., zip code or age).  We will use the financial information that you provide to bill you for products and services.  By giving our Website your credit card and related personal information, you are authorizing our store to give that information to the merchant and credit card company in order to confirm and fulfill your order.  We will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders.  We may also use contact data to get in touch with you when necessary.  We will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval.

h)      **_Information Obtained From Other Sources_**.  Where permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (e.g., mobile devices, third-party services and embedded video players), from co-branded partners and websites (e.g., our Facebook pages) and from commercially available sources (e.g., data on aggregators and public databases).  The following are examples of Your Information that we may collect from other sources:

  * Name, address and telephone number;
  * Demographic data, such as age, gender and income level;
  * Your interests and purchase behavior;
  * Publicly-observed data, such as activities on blogs, videos and other online postings; and
  * Other navigation data, such as websites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on.

i)      **_Combining Information._**   Please note that all of Your Information collected may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across the Mr. Conservative Websites.

j)    **_Usage Or Log Data.   _**Mr. Conservative may gather and analyzes usage or log data including your IP (internet protocol) address assigned by your ISP (internet service provider), the type of operating system you are using on your computer, and the type of web browser you are using to view our Websites. Mr. Conservative management may uses this data to help diagnose problems with and optimize performance of the server.  This information also allows us to evaluate traffic patterns into, out from, and within our Website. These uses, however, do not allow us to connect your IP address to Your Information or otherwise personally identify users.

k)   **_Cookies._**   “Cookies” are small pieces of information your web browser stores on your computer’s hard drive which may contain personally identifying information.  Our Website may place cookies on your computer’s hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide you with certain features. Use of cookies also provides information about your web usage, which helps us compile demographic and statistical information about visitors who are utilizing our Website.  Our advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that.  Disabling cookies for all sites may interfere with your use of some sites. Consult your browser instructions regarding how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

l)        **_Public Forums._**   This Website may host chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.  Any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information, so you should exercise caution before disclosing any personal information.  We cannot safeguard the privacy of any personal information you disclose online in this manner, and you do so at your own risk.

m)      ** _User-Generated Content._**   Some Mr. Conservative Websites enable users to submit their own content, including blogs, videos, message boards, contests, and other functions.  Please remember that any information you disclose in this manner becomes public information, so exercise caution before disclosing any contact, financial and other information in a user content submission.  We cannot prevent such information from being used in violation of this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety.

n)      **_Banner Advertising._**   Mr. Conservative may license ad-server software from other companies to place banner advertising on our Websites.  All data provided and generated by such software will remain in our possession, and no data will be transferred to the licensor of the ad-server software.  This feature of our Websites may, on occasion, set “cookies” on your computer.  Any information collected or stored by the ad-service or the cookies is treated in the same manner as other information as described in this Privacy Policy

o)    **_Feedback Data._**   Some Mr. Conservative Websites allow you to submit feedback.  Feedback data is voluntary information provided by you for the purposes of assessing the products or services provided through Mr. Conservative Websites. Any feedback you submit in these areas becomes the property of Mr. Conservative, and we reserve the right to use this information for the purposes of marketing, quality control, or to contact you for further information.

3. **  Updating and Deleting Personal Data:**

a)      **_Correcting and Updating.   _**You may correct or update your registration data by contacting us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website.

b)      **_Delete/Deactivate._**   You may delete or deactivate your account by either signing into your online account or by contacting us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website and submitting a request to be removed from our database.  Mr. Conservative will comply with all such requests within a reasonable period of time.  Please note that we may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy our legal and security obligations; for example, some of your information may remain in backup storage even if you ask us to delete it.  In some cases, you may be entitled under local laws to access or object to the possession of information that we hold relating to you.

4.  **Information Shared With Third Parties :**

a)      **_Behavioral Advertising._**   Third-party companies may serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information through Audience Management tags when you visit our Websites. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use cookies or web beacons to collect this information.

b)   **_Special Third-Party Relationships_**. Mr. Conservative may enter into special relationships with third-party companies to provide additional features on our Websites.  These special relationships may include “powered by” partners, business partners, sponsors, advertisers, and co-branded sites (referred to here as “co-branded pages”). Any personal information that you provide on any co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partners.  You should check our partner’s privacy policies related to any co-branded pages.  Additionally, the nature of some features of our Website may require that we share personal information about you with persons or companies outside of Mr. Conservative.  For example, this may occur with a feature that enables you, via our Website, to ask questions of persons or entities that are not part of the Mr. Conservative enterprise.  By responding to those features of the Website, whether by email or direct entry of information on our Website, you are consenting to our transferring of that information to such persons or entities.

c)      **_Links to Other Sites._**   When you visit Mr. Conservative Websites, you may be linked to outside sites. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit Your Information. These other sites may be developed by people over whom Mr. Conservative exercises no control and, as such, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Mr. Conservative is not responsible for the privacy policies of these other sites, nor for the use of any of Your Information that these sites may collect.

d)      **_Sale of Our Company._**   Mr. Conservative may include any information we collect through this Website in our customer information database. This database is considered an asset owned by Mr. Conservative. Should another entity ever purchase or acquire Mr. Conservative or its assets, as an entire corporate entity or through an asset sale, all information contained in our customer information database will be considered a transferred asset and become the property of the purchasing or acquiring entity.

5.  **Specific Privacy Rights :**

a)      **_Children’s Privacy._**   Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, this Website does not collect, use or disclose personal information (including online contact information) of children under the age of thirteen (13).  In the event that a child under the age of 13 attempts to register on our Website(s), we will not knowingly accept that registration and will delete information received from the child.  In the event that a child posts personal information in a public forum such as a chat room, we will attempt to delete that information once we become aware of it.

b)      **_Your California Privacy Rights_**.  Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Mr. Conservative who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website.

6.  **Security and Enforcement :**

a) ** _    Information Security._**  The security and confidentiality of Your Information is extremely important to us.  Accordingly, we believe we have appropriate security measures in place, consistent with standard industry practice, to protect against the unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, misuse or destruction of data.  Please be aware, however, that despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.  Accordingly, while we want you to feel confident using the Mr. Conservative Websites, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

b) ** _   Enforcement._**  We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy and will respond accordingly to any formal written complaints, including, if necessary, working with the appropriate regulatory authority to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

7.  **Miscellaneous :**

a)               **_Leased Content_**.  Neither Mr. Conservative nor any third party licensor shall have any liability for the accuracy or completeness of information or services provided via this Website, or for any component thereof, or for delays, inaccuracies, omissions, or other defects therein, nor for any claims or losses arising therefrom, including, without limitation, any lost profits, indirect, special, or consequential damages.  Either Mr. Conservative or third-party licensors have exclusive proprietary rights in the information received via the service. Customers, end-users, or visitors, as applicable, shall not use or permit anyone to use the information provided through the service for any unlawful or unauthorized purpose.  Customers, end-users, or visitors, as applicable, are not authorized or permitted to furnish such information to any person or entity for reuse or retransmission without prior written approval of the source of such information.  Provision of the information on the service is subject to termination in the event that any agreement between a third party licensor and a provider of information distributed through the service is terminated in accordance with its terms.  Third party licensors and their subsidiaries, affiliates, information providers and content partners shall have no liability for actions taken or representations made based on the information provided hereby.

b)   **_Copyright Takedown Notices_**.  If you believe your copyright-protected work has appeared on our Website without authorization, you may submit a copyright notification and takedown request. These requests should only be submitted by the copyright owner or an agent authorized to act on the owner’s behalf.  To make such a notification request, please contact us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website. We accept free-form submissions.

c)   **_Adult Content._** This Website may contain explicit content, including violent images, not intended for viewing by minors or those who do not wish to be exposed to such content.  By registering as a user of this website,  you acknowledge that: You are 18 years old (or older); You will not allow access to any minor (as defined by local law), through action or inaction; and you accept personal responsibility for requesting access to and viewing content on this site. ** __**

d)      **_General Information._**   This Privacy Policy shall be governed by, construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of California, as it is applied to agreements entered into and to be performed entirely within such state, without regard to conflict of law principles. You agree that any cause of action you or Mr. Conservative brings to enforce this Privacy Policy, or in connection with any matters related to this Mr. Conservative Website and/or the Privacy Policy, shall be brought only in either the state or Federal courts located in San Francisco, California. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Califonia for any cause of action arising out of this Privacy Policy.  If any provision of this Privacy Policy, or the application thereof to any person or circumstances, is held invalid or for any reason unenforceable including, but not limited to, applicable Federal, State or local laws or regulations, then such provision shall be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that matches, as closely as possible for purposes of effect, the original provision, and the other provisions of this Policy shall remain in full force and effect.  The failure of either party to insist upon strict performance of any provision of this Privacy Policy shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Unless expressly provided otherwise, this Privacy Policy is the entire agreement between you and Mr. Conservative with respect to the use of this Mr. Conservative Website and shall not be modified except in writing, signed by an authorized representative of Mr. Conservative. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website.

e)      **_European Union and Other Foreign Nations._**   This Mr. Conservative Website is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States of America and is intended for enjoyment of residents of the United States.  Mr. Conservative makes no representation that this Website is governed by or operated in accordance with the laws of other nations.  By using this Website and submitting Your Information, visitors from outside of the United States acknowledge that this Website is subject to U.S. law, consent to the transfer of personal data to the U.S. and waive any claims that may arise under their own national laws.

f)      **_Unsubscribe._**   If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, please contact us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on our Website.  Remember to list each of the email accounts you have given us.

g)      **_Changes to this Policy._**   Mr. Conservative may at any time amend, modify, restate, or revise this Privacy Policy by updating this posting and you should therefore periodically visit this page to view the then current Privacy Policy in effect.  If we make any material changes, we will revise the “Effective and Last Modified” date at the top of the Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of this Website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

h)   **_Legal Disclaimer._**   YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE USING THE WEBSITE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, AND MR. CONSERVATIVE, ITS AFFILIATES AND ITS THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR ANY OTHER WARRANTY, CONDITION, GUARANTEE OR REPRESENTATION, WHETHER ORAL, IN WRITING OR IN ELECTRONIC FORM, INCLUDING BIT NOT LIMITED TO THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREIN OR PROVIDED BY THE WEBSITE. MR. CONSERVATIVE, ITS AFFILIATES, AND ITS THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR THAT THERE WILL BE NO FAILURES, ERRORS OR OMISSIONS OR LOSS OF TRANSMITTED INFORMATION, OR THAT NO VIRUSES WILL BE TRANSMITTED ON THE WEBSITE. MR. CONSERVATIVE, ITS AFFILIATES AND ITS THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ALLEGEDLY SUSTAINED ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT, THE PROVIDING OF THE WEBSITE HEREUNDER, THE SALE OR PURCHASE OF ANY GOODS OR MERCHANDISE, YOUR ACCESS TO OR INABILITY TO ACCESS THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING FOR VIRUSES ALLEGED TO HAVE BEEN OBTAINED FROM THE WEBSITE, YOUR USE OF OR RELIANCE ON THE WEBSITE OR ANY OF THE MERCHANDISE, INFORMATION OR MATERIALS AVAILABLE ON THE WEBSITE, REGARDLESS OF THE TYPE OF CLAIM OR THE NATURE OF THE CAUSE OF ACTION, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE. YOU HEREBY AGREE TO RELEASE MR. CONSERVATIVE, ITS AFFILIATES AND THIRD-PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS FROM CLAIMS, DEMANDS AND DAMAGES (ACTUAL AND CONSEQUENTIAL) OF EVERY KIND AND NATURE, KNOW AND UNKNOWN, SUSPECTED AND UNSUSPECTED, DISCLOSED AND UNDISCLOSED (“CLAIMS”), ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH YOUR USE OF THIS SITE. IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU WAIVE CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE SECTION 1542, WHICH STATES, IN PART: “A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY EFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR”.
